{"data":[{"question":"The Great Depression began _____ the early 1930's.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"There was another protest ____ campus yesterday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"We usually visit our relatives in Vermont _____ Christmas.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- On: taking part in an activity or travelling somewhere","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. Norton gave his presentation _____ the meeting yesterday","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- On: using a machine or piece of equipment\nOn the phone: I am using the phone","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"The company's profits increased substantially _____ fiscal year 2002.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- In: doing or affecting a particular kind of job","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"My garden looks lovely ______ spring.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Unemployment was much lower _____ the third quarter.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n-  Live on something:  to eat a lot of a particular type of food","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Turn left ____ the traffic lights.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- In: into a container, place\n She's inside the office","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"I often go skiing _____ winter.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"I'll call you ____ half past ten","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- In: doing or affecting a particular kind of job","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"}]}